[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Our next step is to evaluate
下一步就是来评估
the sentiment model that we've built.
我们建立的情感分析模型
Now, we just talked in this module about classification error,
在之前的章节提到过的分类误差
precision, sorry, false positives and false negatives.
准确率 噢不对应该是假阳性和假阴性
And we're gonna explore that idea right here
我们要在这个Notebook里研究
in this demonstration in this notebook.
这个概念
So the sentiment model has a function called Evaluate.
情感分析模型有着一个叫做Evalute（评估）的函数
And that function Evaluate allows you to evaluate its quality on some test data.
这个Evaluate 函数能够让你去评估你测试数据的结果 质量
And we're gonna provide a particular metric and
我们会提供一个特定的计量标准
this metric is called the roc_curve.
并且把这个计量标准叫做ROC曲线（受试者工作特征曲线）
And we're gonna learn a little bit more about the roc_curve next.
我们接下来的内容就是和这个ROC曲线相关
But the roc_curve is a way to explore the false positives and
但是ROC曲线只是用来研究
false negatives in that confusion matrix that we discussed.
在混淆矩阵中假阳性和假阴性的 我们之前也说过这点
Now, here is, it shows you the results of evaluations that are hard to see in text.
这边它给你显示了评估结果 用文本格式看起来比较费力
So let's do a little visualization of it, again, using Canvas.
让我们做一点可视化 我们还是会用到Canvas
So we can use sentiment_model.show, and
我们可以输入sentiment_model.show(这个代码）
we're gonna show the view that we're gonna use,
然后就能看到我们将要用到的东西了（这一步是在可视化）
is going to be the Evaluation view.
这就是我们评估结果的图
And here we go.
我们去到这里
Okay, this is really cool.
看起来真的很酷
We've built a few things.
我们建立了一些内容
So this is a precision recall, I'm sorry, this is what is called an roc_curve,
这是精确率 召回率 噢不对 应该是ROC 曲线
it's a curve that trades off false positives with true positives.
这个曲线是关于假阳性和真阳性的取舍
Let me explain that a little bit.
让我稍稍解释一下
But first, let's look at these numbers over here.
让我们看一些这边的数字
So this is the confusion matrix.
这是混淆矩阵
The number of true positives,
真阳性的数量
the things that we got right that were true, is 26,455.
就是事实上是正的样本 而我们预测的也是正的样本，它的数量是26455
So right here.
在这里
The number of true negatives was only 4,000, so 3,965.
真阴性的数目只有不到4000 3965个
So this is a highly unbalanced case.
是一个非常不平衡的例子
And then, the number of false positives and
假阳性的数目
the number of false negatives is about the same.
和假阴性的数目大致相等
The overall accuracy was 91.1%, so 0.911.
所以说总体的准确率是在91.1% 也就是0.911
And also discuss a few metrics like precision recall and false count
我们讨论过一些计量标准 像精确召回 还有错误计数
which we're gonna learn more about later in the course and later in specialization.
我们要在以后的课程中学到这些
Now, the thing about the false positives and false negatives is that
现在的问题是 关于假阳性和假阴性
there's a very natural way to change the threshold of what we believe
如果我们改变了我们之前认为的临界值
the transition from negative class to positive class should be.
那么从阴性转变到阳性就会是一个很自然的转变
So this is what the threshold shows on the right, but
所以我们右边显示的临界值
let me first show it on the curve here.
让我把它放到我们的ROC曲线上
So, you can see it is possible for me to get, for
你可以看到 对我来说  很可能会得到
example, a very high true positive rate.
一个很高的真阳性率
So .4, if I, sorry, a very low .4.
应该是0.4 噢不对应该是一个很低的真阳性率 0.4
If I dont' allow myself to get any false positives.
在我不让自己得到任何一个假阳性的情况下
So, if I'm very worried about false positives that can be very conservative,
也就是说我是很担心假阳性 所以我就比较保守
get no false positives.
这样就不会得到假阳性
But again not capture many of the true positives and make other mistakes.
但是再一次地 没有捕捉到很多真阳性 并犯了别的错误
And you see.
你可以看到
As you go through the curve there's a kink here.
这个曲线有一个拐点
This is the point where you get not too many false positives but
这个点就是当你并没有很多假阳性但是
a lot of true positives.
有很多真阳性的点
And then over on this end you get every true positive.
在右边的端点 你每一个点都是真阳性
But you get a lot of false positives.
但是你也会得到很多假阳性
How do you get every true positive but get less false positives?
所以说你要怎么样 才能得到很多的真阳性 但是又要保证比较低的假阳性呢
You just say every data point is positive.
你可以预测每个数据都是阳性
Then you get all the true positives, but you also make a lot of mistakes.
然后你会得到很多的真阳性 但是你犯了了很多错误
And, we'll discuss more of this when we talk about precision recall curve.
我们会在精确召回曲线中讨论更多关于这个
But, nicely, we can change the threshold over here, and walk that curve up there.
不过在这里 我们能通过改变临界值 来做到
As you can see, and so for example, the far end, on the right,
你看举个例子 在很右边很远的端点
you see that the true positive rate is really high.
真阳性的值很高
There's no false positives, but that there's no true negatives.
但是没有假阴性 也没有真阴性
So there's no false negatives, no true negatives, you just got everything right.
但是没有假阴性 也没有真阴性 你预测的都是阳性
And then you can slide it just the other way.
你可以滑动这个断点
So you can play with this and
这样你就能来改变一些东西
really kind of get a good sense of what this curve really means, the roc_curve.
也能够理解这条roc曲线真正意味着什么
And that's the evaluation that we're gonna be doing.
这就是我们所做的评估
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community